All right, Dan. So, Kate Mays was able
to go and secure himself the bag. He got
the bag. That's I mean, that's what you
play for, man. You You want to go out,
you want to play well enough that your
own team can either resign you and if
they're not able to that somebody else
will take advantage of signing you. And
shout out to Kade.
But we had the opportunity to sign Luke
Forner, a guy that we played against.
Yeah.
>> Couple times a year coming from the New
Orleans Saints.
>> What did you identify in Luke Forner
that made you feel like he can be a guy
that can come in and play for us right
away? One of the things that I've
learned about him though is that he's
very smart.
>> Super smart.
>> Super smart. Three degrees. Something
that you know
>> like aerospace engineering or something
like that.
>> Why is that important for a center to be
smart? Well, I mean, the center, as you
know, runs the show, right? So, like,
for him to be out there and understand
the protections and understand what the
defense is doing, I mean, that's
invaluable. So, to have a guy that smart
and also have the athleticism and
understanding of angles and ability to
climb to the second level, um, that's
what attracted us to him.
>> Does that help Bryce in any way? Yeah, I
mean I think, you know, it takes a
little bit off Bryce's plate, you know,
where you you have a guy that can
identify, set the protections, and
really you can take that off Bryce's
plate if you want to. Now, Bryce likes
to have that and be in control, but at
the same time, if we needed him to do
that, you know, if an injury occurred or
something like that, this is a guy that
can run the show.
>> All right, so let's let's identify what
he does on the field. We talked about
how smart he is. Let's see some of his
athleticism.
>> He's he's a tough dude. You know, when
you meet him, he's he's a great guy. Uh
really good culture guy, really good
locker room guy. Um but he's really
good. He's technical. He's good with his
angles. Um he just knows how to play the
position. You nastiness to him, too,
though. If you watch that finish on the
end of this one,
>> he does.
>> Okay. Does his job finishes. That's what
you want out of a offensive lineman, a
guy that's going to finish. These are
the type of guys that we all hate it,
you know. Yeah. Is he like the biggest
guy? No. But he's tough, takes good
angles, he knows how to get in position.
>> Annoying as hell. Those are the guys
you're talking about.
>> Especially for like us us type of
linebackers that are fast flow type guys
and all of a sudden they get up to you.
You have a decision to make.
>> Do you go over top or do you slip them
underneath, you know?
>> But again, right here, like, yeah, is he
knocking people off the ball? No. But
he's good with angles. He's doing his
job. He's doing his job. He's He's
creating the lane for the running back.
And that's what we need.
>> Y
>> consistent play out of the center.
That's going to be
>> every single play doing his job the
right way every single time. And you
bring a guy in that can do that, you can
have confidence and other guys alongside
of him can have confidence that, hey,
he's going to be where he needs to be.
He's going to be 111th of this offense.
again right here. You see just like the
the angles and how flat he gets and like
to cut a fast flow linebacker off. I
mean, look at the lane it creates.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, next thing you know, it's six,
seven, eight yards downfield.
>> And that's Deion Jones, too. So, we know
how fast he is. We've got to play
against him. He played for us and now
he's playing
>> for the for Tampa Bay. So, we know that
this guy is fast. So to see him be able
to climb up to him
>> and seal him off,
>> I love to see it.
>> And that, you know, and then the one
thing sometimes that goes unnoticed too
is like how accurate his snaps are, too.
Like some some centers, you know,
they're not as accurate with their snaps
and it kind of,
>> you know, it can throw the timing of
plays off. So this guy's really good
with his snaps and just kind of running
the show out there.
>> We saw a few high snaps last year. So
>> yeah,
>> got to be consistent. That's the biggest
key. Like if you're going to be if
you're going to be consistent and you
know as a quarterback what to expect.
You know what you're going to get. The
guys, like I said, next to you know what
you're going to bring to the table. You
love having those kind of players. I see
the athleticism on pulls and and
screens. What kind of impact does he
have in those particular plays? And we
know the Saints love to run screens.
>> Yep. Yeah. And you know, hopefully
that's something that we get better at
as a team, especially having a more
athletic center, a guy that can get out
in space and, you know, execute a block
in space versus a linebacker that's a
moving target.
>> Y
>> um again, it's not easy and, you know,
he can make it look easy sometimes.
>> Doesn't have to be a huge huge blow up.
Yeah.
>> Sometimes all you need to do is just get
in the way where the guy can't make the
play. That's what he does. Again, just
another example of just like initial
quickness, good angles, good use of
hands, like
>> and staying connected.
>> Yep.
>> All right.
>> Just knows how to play
>> and finishing downfield. How many yards
downfield was that?
>> 10.
>> Yeah. 10 15
>> yards. So, I mean, you love you love to
see that guys committed to taking look,
you're like, you going to run all the
way down field with me.
>> So, I would say all in all, man, you
guys did a phenomenal job. Love the new
pieces. And then if you factor in this
free agency along with it's almost like
we got another free agent piece when we
get Pat Jones back who we lost for most
of the season last year
>> as well. So
>> yeah, we got a lot of versatility up
front.
>> Yeah, man. The sky the sky is really the
limit for this defense. I'm looking
forward to seeing what we're going to be
able to do in the draft and how you're
going to close out free agency. So man,
we appreciate
>> we definitely appreciate you taking the
time to sit with us and kind of
>> share with our fan base, you know, what
goes into the mindset of being able to
make these decisions. I mean, I know a a
lot of our fan base are extremely
excited about the moves that we've made
so far. I mean, and we didn't even talk
about some of the other guys that we
were able to bring in as well. So, a lot
of lot of added value to this football
team. So, Dan, we'll appreciate you.
>> Appreciate you, man.